<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>baby photo session | Photo shoots</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/baby-photo-session/</link><atom:link href="https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/baby-photo-session/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>baby photo session</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2023 Viktoria Iljin</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 06:09:53 +0300</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://www.lastefoto.ee/media/sharing.jpg</url><title>baby photo session</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/baby-photo-session/</link></image><item><title>The Newborn and Maternity Festival in Tallinn</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/newbornfest-2023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 06:09:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/newbornfest-2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>As newborn and maternity photographers, we know the importance of capturing the beauty and joy of new life. That is why we are excited to announce the first annual Newborn and Maternity Festival, taking place in Tallinn in 2023.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>This event will bring together photographers from around the world to celebrate the art of newborn and maternity photography and learn from some of the industry&amp;rsquo;s top professionals.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>The NewbornFest will be a two-day event featuring lectures, performances and group workshops from some of the most respected photographers in the industry. Whether you are a seasoned pro or just starting out in newborn and maternity photography, there will be something for everyone at the festival.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One of the highlights of the festival will be the opportunity to learn from some of the best in the business. Our lineup of speakers includes award-winning photographers who have years of experience capturing the beauty and emotion of newborn and maternity photography. From lighting techniques to composition tips, these photographers will share their knowledge and expertise to help you improve your craft.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But the NewbornFest isn&amp;rsquo;t just about learning and improving your craft – it&amp;rsquo;s also about networking and making connections with other photographers. The festival will provide ample opportunity for attendees to meet and mingle with their peers, exchange ideas, and potentially even land new clients. It&amp;rsquo;s a chance to be a part of a community of photographers who share a passion for newborn and maternity photography.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But the fun doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to end when the festival is over. Tallinn, the capital of Estonia, is a beautiful and vibrant city with plenty to see and do. From its charming old town to its modern city center, there is something for everyone in Tallinn. The festival will also offer a number of social events and activities for attendees to enjoy, including Newborn Props Fair and group dinner.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The NewbornFest is an exciting opportunity for photographers to learn, grow, and connect with their peers. We hope you will join us in Tallinn in 2023 for this inaugural event.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on the chance to be a part of something special – we look forward to seeing you there!&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul class="cta-group">
&lt;li>
&lt;a href="https://www.newbornfest.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="btn btn-primary px-3 py-3">Get your ticket to the NewbornFest 2023&lt;/a>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Baby photo shoot during the first year of life</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/baby-photo-shoot-during-the-first-year-of-life/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 06:09:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/baby-photo-shoot-during-the-first-year-of-life/</guid><description>&lt;p>A photo shoot with a newborn or one taken at 3, 6, or 9 months - which is preferable? In order to get the most variety of images, how many photo shootings per year are ideal? Such questions are frequently made by young parents. Additionally, while the frequency of photo shootings is decided by each family individually based on their preferences and finances, the details of photo shoots at each age may be worthwhile as a recommendation.&lt;/p>
&lt;figure id="figure-baby-photo-shoot-in-tallinn">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./baby-photo-shoot-1.jpg" alt="Baby photo shoot in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Baby photo shoot in Tallinn
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;h2 id="baby-photo-shoot---important-details">Baby photo shoot - important details&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Although parents frequently feel that it is &amp;ldquo;too early,&amp;rdquo; now is the ideal time for a photo shoot if your baby has just been born. The baby normally sleeps soundly, so they aren&amp;rsquo;t even aware of posing or switching between props. Additionally, it is also very important to note that babies often do not experience colic at this time.&lt;/p>
&lt;figure id="figure-baby-photo-shoot">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./baby-photo-shoot-2.jpg" alt="Baby photo shoot" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Baby photo shoot
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;h2 id="what-a-photo-shoot-with-an-older-baby-should-look-like">What a photo shoot with an older baby should look like&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>It is preferable to delay the photo session for babies older than four weeks until they are three months old. At this age, colic can be relatively frequent, which makes sleeping habits more disturbed and shortens the amount of time a baby is awake for a proper photo shoot.&lt;/p>
&lt;figure id="figure-baby-photo-session-in-the-studio-in-tallinn">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./baby-photo-shoot-3.jpg" alt="Baby photo session in the studio in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Baby photo session in the studio in Tallinn
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>If for whatever reason you didn&amp;rsquo;t have time to take a photo shoot during the newborn period, it&amp;rsquo;s time to consider one if the baby is three months old and colic is well behind the baby. In this case, attention is being paid to the baby&amp;rsquo;s waking periods, feelings, and familiarity with toys and  world around him. By the way, babies fit perfectly well in baskets and other similar props at this age, as well as at 4-5 months, though they rarely agree to sleep in them any longer, but they still look very cute.&lt;/p>
&lt;figure id="figure-babys-first-birthday-photo-shoot-in-the-studio-in-tallinn">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./baby-photo-shoot-4.jpg" alt="Baby&amp;#39;s first birthday photo shoot in the studio in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Baby&amp;rsquo;s first birthday photo shoot in the studio in Tallinn
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>Babies are learning to sit up on their own at 6-7 months, which greatly expands the number of shot scenarios available. If you plan a photo shoot around this time, you&amp;rsquo;ll get a lot of great shots.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Photographing a baby at 8-9 months is difficult because they are constantly trying to get out of the shot, wiggle around, and explore everything within their reach. However, nothing is impossible for a baby photographer, so even if you are completely unable to capture your baby, a professional baby photographer will succeed.&lt;/p>
&lt;video controls >
&lt;source src="https://www.lastefoto.ee/media/Minu%20esimene%20eluaasta.mp4" type="video/mp4">
&lt;/video>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure id="figure-babys-first-year-photo-shoots-in-tallinn">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./baby-first-year.jpg" alt="Baby&amp;#39;s first year photo shoots in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Baby&amp;rsquo;s first year photo shoots in Tallinn
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure id="figure-framed-pictures-as-a-result-of-photo-shoots">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./framed-picture.jpg" alt="Framed pictures as a result of photo shoots" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Framed pictures as a result of photo shoots
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure id="figure-photobook-details">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./photobook-2.jpg" alt="Photobook, details" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Photobook, details
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;figure id="figure-photobook-detais">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./photobook-3.jpg" alt="Photobook, detais" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Photobook, detais
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>&lt;/p>
&lt;ul class="cta-group">
&lt;li>
&lt;a href="https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/#contact" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="btn btn-primary px-3 py-3">Book baby photo shoot&lt;/a>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>