<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>maternity | Photo shoots</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/maternity/</link><atom:link href="https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/maternity/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>maternity</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2024 Viktoria Iljin</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 06:09:53 +0300</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://www.lastefoto.ee/media/sharing.jpg</url><title>maternity</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/maternity/</link></image><item><title>The Newborn and Maternity Festival in Tallinn</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/newbornfest-2023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 06:09:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/newbornfest-2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>As newborn and maternity photographers, we know the importance of capturing the beauty and joy of new life. That is why we are excited to announce the first annual Newborn and Maternity Festival, taking place in Tallinn in 2023.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>This event will bring together photographers from around the world to celebrate the art of newborn and maternity photography and learn from some of the industry&amp;rsquo;s top professionals.&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;p>The NewbornFest will be a two-day event featuring lectures, performances and group workshops from some of the most respected photographers in the industry. Whether you are a seasoned pro or just starting out in newborn and maternity photography, there will be something for everyone at the festival.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One of the highlights of the festival will be the opportunity to learn from some of the best in the business. Our lineup of speakers includes award-winning photographers who have years of experience capturing the beauty and emotion of newborn and maternity photography. From lighting techniques to composition tips, these photographers will share their knowledge and expertise to help you improve your craft.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But the NewbornFest isn&amp;rsquo;t just about learning and improving your craft – it&amp;rsquo;s also about networking and making connections with other photographers. The festival will provide ample opportunity for attendees to meet and mingle with their peers, exchange ideas, and potentially even land new clients. It&amp;rsquo;s a chance to be a part of a community of photographers who share a passion for newborn and maternity photography.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But the fun doesn&amp;rsquo;t have to end when the festival is over. Tallinn, the capital of Estonia, is a beautiful and vibrant city with plenty to see and do. From its charming old town to its modern city center, there is something for everyone in Tallinn. The festival will also offer a number of social events and activities for attendees to enjoy, including Newborn Props Fair and group dinner.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The NewbornFest is an exciting opportunity for photographers to learn, grow, and connect with their peers. We hope you will join us in Tallinn in 2023 for this inaugural event.&lt;/p>
&lt;blockquote>
&lt;p>Don&amp;rsquo;t miss out on the chance to be a part of something special – we look forward to seeing you there!&lt;/p>
&lt;/blockquote>
&lt;ul class="cta-group">
&lt;li>
&lt;a href="https://www.newbornfest.com" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="btn btn-primary px-3 py-3">Get your ticket to the NewbornFest 2023&lt;/a>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>