<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>newborn photo session | Photo shoots</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/newborn-photo-session/</link><atom:link href="https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/newborn-photo-session/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>newborn photo session</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2023 Viktoria Iljin</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 06:09:53 +0300</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://www.lastefoto.ee/media/sharing.jpg</url><title>newborn photo session</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/newborn-photo-session/</link></image><item><title>Newborn photo session - safety in every detail</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/newborn-photo-session/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 06:09:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/newborn-photo-session/</guid><description>&lt;p>Newborn photo session can be a stressful experience for new parents, as mums and dads need to make sure the photo session is safe for their little one.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="newborn-photo-session-important-details-for-a-safe-photo-shoot">Newborn photo session: Important details for a safe photo shoot&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>No contact with a huge number of people - as your baby&amp;rsquo;s immune system doesn&amp;rsquo;t need such a burden. For this reason, many parents opt for a home photo session for their newborn baby, but it can also be done at the studio. Don&amp;rsquo;t believe that? Come and visit my cosy studio right away. Only a baby, his family and a photographer are there at the moment of shooting.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Cleanliness. Absolute and perfect cleanliness in the studio is the key to a safe newborn photo session. In order to achieve this, I do wet cleaning before each photo shoot, and I wash all the props used for the photo session after its finishing.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Comfortable temperature and lighting. The most important thing in a newborn photo shoot is the comfort of the little model. To make the baby sleep well it is very warm in the studio. In the cold off-season I use an extra heater, so parents often find it hot in the studio. But the babies strongly disagree - they sleep just fine at this temperature. I use a variety of professional equipment for the lighting, which doesn&amp;rsquo;t harm the baby&amp;rsquo;s eyes, even if I&amp;rsquo;m doing portraits of a non-sleeping baby.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Only safe poses. All of the poses I use to photograph newborns are absolutely safe for the baby. If I think that your child is in any way at risk I either ask the parents for support or I just change the pose.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;figure id="figure-newborn-photo-session">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photo-session.jpg" alt="Newborn photo session" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Newborn photo session
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>It is not difficult to safely take a picture of a newborn if you have all the details of the upcoming photo session in mind. There is no need to fear that the baby could be harmed in any way - the professionalism of a newborn photographer is just that: to make the newborn photo session completely safe and comfortable for the little model.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul class="cta-group">
&lt;li>
&lt;a href="https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/#contact" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="btn btn-primary px-3 py-3">Book newborn photo session&lt;/a>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Newborn photo shoots - you have to prepare in advance</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/newborn-photo-shoots/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 06:09:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/newborn-photo-shoots/</guid><description>&lt;p>Newborn photo shoots are becoming increasingly popular in our country. For many parents, along with packing things for the maternity hospital, buying baby clothes and other things to do before the baby is born, &amp;ldquo;finding a newborn photographer&amp;rdquo; is an important point on the &amp;ldquo;list of things to do before the baby is born&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="newborn-photographer-when-to-start-looking">Newborn photographer: when to start looking?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The correct answer to this question is &amp;ldquo;the sooner the better&amp;rdquo;. Around the second trimester of pregnancy, when toxicosis passes and the mother-to-be gets used to her new status, it is possible and even necessary to look for a newborn photographer without haste and fuss. At this time, you can quietly review the portfolio, choosing a few newborn photographers whose work you like best. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to ask your friends to recommend professionals - personal experience is always better.
Before you decide, it&amp;rsquo;s worth talking to the newborn photographer in person or at least on the phone. Try to understand how comfortable you feel with this person.&lt;/p>
&lt;figure id="figure-newborn-photo-shoots-in-tallinn">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photo-shoots.jpg" alt="Newborn photo shoots in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Newborn photo shoots in Tallinn
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;h2 id="newborn-photo-shoot-how-to-book-a-date-for-your-newborn-photo-shoot">Newborn photo shoot: how to book a date for your newborn photo shoot?&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>The best time for a newborn photo shoots is when your baby is newborn - that is, until he or she is 28 days from birth. However, more often than not, newborn photographers prefer to work with babies under two weeks of age, as this is when babies sleep soundly and sweetly. This is why newborn photo shoots should definitely be booked in advance - ideally a couple of months before the photo shoot, because if the newborn photographer is popular, his schedule is usually packed quite tightly.
However, a couple of months before the photo shoot, it&amp;rsquo;s completely impossible to predict exactly what day your baby will be born, so booking your newborn photo shoot date is based on the expected due date. Therefore, as soon as your baby arrives, you should let the photographer know about it as soon as possible so that the photographer can find a day for a newborn photo shoot that suits both of you. Recommendations on preparations should be obtained from the newborn photographer in advance, but in general, the photographer will take care of most of the things. All you have to do is relax and fully enjoy the process.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul class="cta-group">
&lt;li>
&lt;a href="https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/#contact" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="btn btn-primary px-3 py-3">Book newborn photo shoot&lt;/a>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>