<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>cake smash | Newborn photographer</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/category/cake-smash/</link><atom:link href="https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/category/cake-smash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>cake smash</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 17:45:53 +0200</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://www.lastefoto.ee/media/sharing.jpg</url><title>cake smash</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/category/cake-smash/</link></image><item><title>Cake Smash photosession</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/cake-smash-first-photosession/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 17:45:53 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/cake-smash-first-photosession/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="how-funny-these-yearlings-are">How funny these &amp;ldquo;yearlings&amp;rdquo; are!&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I really want to forever leave in my memory their insecure club-footed steps and a look full of delight from the incredible discoveries that happen EVERY TIME in the life of a little person!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That is why, on the first birthday of the baby, many parents choose a thematic &lt;strong>CAKE SMASH&lt;/strong> photosession!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./cake-smash-first-photosession-1.jpg" alt="cake smash photosession" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Colored glaze on the cheeks, bursting laughter and the opportunity to smear everything around with cake - isn&amp;rsquo;t this happiness for the birthday man?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>But this shooting has a couple of nuances that you should know about in advance so that reality does not diverge from your colorful expectations. Now I will tell you about them.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./cake-smash-first-photosession-2.jpg" alt="cake smash session" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>There are chances that your normally active and inquisitive baby will get scared of the cake.
This is really a big and scary thing. So get ready to join the confectionery wreck with your baby!&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./cake-smash-first-photosession-3.jpg" alt="cake smash photosession in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>It will be great if you have two sets of clothes with you: one for a dignified and noble family shooting at the beginning and the other - for greasy stains from cream and filling at the end.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Since photo session is a very emotional event, especially if you can smear something on the face and the floor, then it is better not to do it on the birth day itself: the baby may have too many impressions.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./cake-smash-first-photosession-4.jpg" alt="cake smash photosession in studio" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>For the same reason, be sure to consider the rhythm of the child&amp;rsquo;s sleep and wakefulness when choosing the time to shoot, so that fatigue does not affect our funny session in any way.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>I myself can take care of a suitable cake. But if you certainly want to bring your own, then consult with me in advance: I will suggest the subtleties that are important for the visual component of the &amp;ldquo;CAKE SMASH&amp;rdquo; photo session.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Smiles to you, sweet treats and memorable frames! ♥ Sign up for shooting!&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>