<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>baby session | Photo shoots</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/baby-session/</link><atom:link href="https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/baby-session/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>baby session</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2023 Viktoria Iljin</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 06:09:53 +0300</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://www.lastefoto.ee/media/sharing.jpg</url><title>baby session</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/baby-session/</link></image><item><title>Features of a baby photo shoot - become friends with the little model</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/features-of-a-baby-photo-shoot/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 06:09:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/features-of-a-baby-photo-shoot/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="baby-photo-shoot-a-wonderful-world-of-emotions-and-fun">Baby photo shoot: A Wonderful World of Emotions and Fun&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Baby photo shoot is a kind of magic. This is an art direction that requires unsurpassed dexterity and patience, because the baby, the main character, can be a real prankster. He won&amp;rsquo;t always sit still or strike intended poses, but it&amp;rsquo;s this unpredictability that makes baby photography so amazing. The flash of emotion that you capture will be unique and cannot be compared with any other genre.&lt;/p>
&lt;figure id="figure-baby-photo-shoot-in-tallinn">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./features-of-a-baby-photo-shoot-1.jpg" alt="Baby photo shoot in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Baby photo shoot in Tallinn
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;h2 id="baby-photography-basics">Baby photography basics&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>How is the baby photo session going? This is a question without a specific answer, because each session is unique and reflects the individuality of the baby. For example, some kids love to have fun and be entertained, whether in the studio, outdoors, or at home, while actively exploring new spaces. The task of the baby photographer here is only to catch unique shots.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>At the same time, others may be more modest and prefer to retire to a corner. It is important to give such a child time to adapt and not rush him.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The main rule of baby photography is no rigid posing. Children behave naturally and spontaneously, and the baby photographer only captures interesting moments through the lens.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Outdoor photo shoots are often especially successful. Just head to the nearest playground - many of them have quite a beautiful and photogenic design. In such conditions, you will only have to keep up with an actively moving baby, who feels like a fish in water in a familiar environment.&lt;/p>
&lt;figure id="figure-baby-photo-shoot-in-the-studio">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./features-of-a-baby-photo-shoot-2.jpg" alt="Baby photo shoot in the studio" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Baby photo shoot in the studio
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;h2 id="becoming-friends-with-a-little-one">Becoming friends with a little one&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Considering that baby photography requires natural behavior, getting along with a small model is extremely important. A children&amp;rsquo;s photographer should be patient and not rushed, create a friendly atmosphere, communicate with the baby, offer games and engage in interesting activities with him. The most successful shots are obtained when the baby is completely immersed in his own activities and forgets about the presence of the photographer.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>If the photo shoot takes place in the studio, taking your child&amp;rsquo;s favourite toy with you may be a good idea. This will help him quickly adapt to an unfamiliar environment.&lt;/p>
&lt;figure id="figure-baby-photo-shoot">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./features-of-a-baby-photo-shoot-3.jpg" alt="Baby photo shoot" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Baby photo shoot
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;h2 id="appreciate-the-moment">Appreciate the moment&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>Taking baby pictures can be a time consuming process, but the gorgeous, vibrant and emotional images you end up with are well worth the effort. Don&amp;rsquo;t wait for your little one to grow up - capture those moments of youth now.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul class="cta-group">
&lt;li>
&lt;a href="https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/#contact" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="btn btn-primary px-3 py-3">Book baby photo shoot&lt;/a>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item><item><title>Newborn photo shoot: the color of memories. Newborn photographer tips.</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/newborn-session-the-colour-of-memories-newborn-photographer-tips/</link><pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 10:00:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/newborn-session-the-colour-of-memories-newborn-photographer-tips/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have already written about the most appropriate time to shoot a newborn, about the most touching poses &amp;hellip; And today I want to touch on the topic of color.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photographer-1.jpg" alt="newborn photo shoot" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Before the newborn session, parents receive a questionnaire from me, one of the points of which is the choice of the color in which the newborn photo shoot will take place. I have fifteen of them to choose from, both for boys and girls.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photographer-2.jpg" alt="newborn photo shoot in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>It would seem that everything is simple: the color of my husband&amp;rsquo;s favorite football team is red, I also always liked this color: energetic, bright &amp;hellip; take it!&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photographer-3.jpg" alt="newborn session in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>BUT.
Will scarlet pictures fit into the interior of your home?
And if the baby was born with a distinctly reddish skin tone, are you sure you want to further accentuate it with items of clothing and props? Or, nevertheless, on the contrary, is it better to level this redness with green?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photographer-4.jpg" alt="newborn session in the studio" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There are such subtleties that you cannot immediately think of.
But now that you know about them, what color would you choose? Classic blue/pink? Or something more extravagant?&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photographer-5.jpg" alt="newborn photo shoot in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>How to choose a newborn photographer</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/how-to-choose-a-newborn-photographer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2021 10:00:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/post/how-to-choose-a-newborn-photographer/</guid><description>&lt;p>Choosing a photographer for your newborn baby is a very responsible thing. The newborn photography market is developing very quickly and a large number of photographers offer their services.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;em>How not to be mistaken with the choice?&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>After all, you do not just choose a photographer, you choose a specialist who will make a photo shoot professionally and safely for the baby.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photographer-1.jpg" alt="newborn photo shoot" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Start looking for your photographer while you are pregnant. When the baby is born, you simply will not have time for this. And the ideal time (4-15 days) for a photo shoot of a newborn passes imperceptibly.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photographer-2.jpg" alt="newborn photo shoot in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Choose a photographer who specializes in newborn photography. Browse through the portfolio. If necessary, ask a photographer to show you a series of photo shoots so you can better understand if a particular style of photography is right for you.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photographer-3.jpg" alt="newborn session in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Read reviews from other customers. Ask how long the photographer has specialized in newborn photoshoots, where and from whom he studied.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photographer-4.jpg" alt="newborn photo shoot in Tallinn" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>Don&amp;rsquo;t choose a photographer based solely on the price of a photo shoot. The price of a newborn photo shoot cannot be low - in addition to the necessary props, which must be purchased and prepared for the photo shoot, a professional newborn photographer must study a lot in order not only to please you with beautiful pictures, but also to ensure the safety of your baby during the photo shoot. Safety is the most important thing in a newborn photo shoot.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>Of course, the price of a newborn photo shoot is very important, but don&amp;rsquo;t make it the main criterion.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>
&lt;figure >
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photographer-5.jpg" alt="newborn session in the studio" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;/figure>
&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Choose a photographer for your baby, who will give you pictures, looking at which you will remember how tiny your baby was, how thin his fingers were and how you wanted to kiss his sweet toes. ❤️&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>