<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>newborn photo sessions | Photo shoots</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/newborn-photo-sessions/</link><atom:link href="https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/newborn-photo-sessions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>newborn photo sessions</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2024 Viktoria Iljin</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 06:09:53 +0300</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://www.lastefoto.ee/media/sharing.jpg</url><title>newborn photo sessions</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/tag/newborn-photo-sessions/</link></image><item><title>Newborn photo session - safety in every detail</title><link>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/newborn-photo-session/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Mar 2023 06:09:53 +0300</pubDate><guid>https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/newborn-photo-session/</guid><description>&lt;p>Newborn photo session can be a stressful experience for new parents, as mums and dads need to make sure the photo session is safe for their little one.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="newborn-photo-session-important-details-for-a-safe-photo-shoot">Newborn photo session: Important details for a safe photo shoot&lt;/h2>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>No contact with a huge number of people - as your baby&amp;rsquo;s immune system doesn&amp;rsquo;t need such a burden. For this reason, many parents opt for a home photo session for their newborn baby, but it can also be done at the studio. Don&amp;rsquo;t believe that? Come and visit my cosy studio right away. Only a baby, his family and a photographer are there at the moment of shooting.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Cleanliness. Absolute and perfect cleanliness in the studio is the key to a safe newborn photo session. In order to achieve this, I do wet cleaning before each photo shoot, and I wash all the props used for the photo session after its finishing.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Comfortable temperature and lighting. The most important thing in a newborn photo shoot is the comfort of the little model. To make the baby sleep well it is very warm in the studio. In the cold off-season I use an extra heater, so parents often find it hot in the studio. But the babies strongly disagree - they sleep just fine at this temperature. I use a variety of professional equipment for the lighting, which doesn&amp;rsquo;t harm the baby&amp;rsquo;s eyes, even if I&amp;rsquo;m doing portraits of a non-sleeping baby.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Only safe poses. All of the poses I use to photograph newborns are absolutely safe for the baby. If I think that your child is in any way at risk I either ask the parents for support or I just change the pose.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;figure id="figure-newborn-photo-session">
&lt;div class="d-flex justify-content-center">
&lt;div class="w-100" >&lt;img src="./newborn-photo-session.jpg" alt="Newborn photo session" loading="lazy" data-zoomable />&lt;/div>
&lt;/div>&lt;figcaption>
Newborn photo session
&lt;/figcaption>&lt;/figure>
&lt;p>It is not difficult to safely take a picture of a newborn if you have all the details of the upcoming photo session in mind. There is no need to fear that the baby could be harmed in any way - the professionalism of a newborn photographer is just that: to make the newborn photo session completely safe and comfortable for the little model.&lt;/p>
&lt;ul class="cta-group">
&lt;li>
&lt;a href="https://www.lastefoto.ee/en/#contact" target="_blank" rel="noopener" class="btn btn-primary px-3 py-3">Book newborn photo session&lt;/a>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul></description></item></channel></rss>